Hyginus Ukeh

Federal Capital Territory, Nigeria



linkedin.com/in/hyginus-ukeh-b2931215b



hyginusukeh6@gmail.com



http://www.hyginusukeh.com



08068208406

Summary

I'm a full-stack developer with 5 years of coding experience and two (2) years in the professional industry.

I create UI Designs using Figma, then convert to web pages using HTML, CSS and Javascript. I was part of a team that built a web-based estate management system using React JS and Java. Lately, I am currently working on a transaction processing web-based application, that handles bulk payments using React and Laravel (PHP).

I also share some UI tutorial contents on YouTube. I love learning, teaching and playing football games.

Experience



Full-stack Software Engineer

Techvibesltd

Mar 2018 - Present (2 years 3 months +)

- Integrated several Payment Switches for existing and new web applications.
- Worked as a team in building a React Web-Based Application.
- Developed a Transaction Processing Web-Based Application with Laravel (PHP).
- Revamped existing Product UI's.
- Built a content management system using WordPress.
- Converting Figma Designs to Web Pages.

Technologies: React, Redux, Laravel (PHP), MySql, Git, Heroku, Trello, Slack, WordPress, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Window Server.



CUSTOMER CARE OFFICER

GTBank

Feb 2014 - Feb 2015 (1 year 1 month)

- Awarded the best Industrial Trannie of the year (2015).
- I enrolled Gtbank Customers into the Bank Verification System (BVN).
- I assisted in uploading new customer's accounts into the banking system.
- Managed existing and new customer's files and instructions.
- Bulk teller for some few months.
- Helped in troubleshooting and fixing minor system issues.

Education



Institute of Management and Technology, IMT Enugu

Higher National Diploma, Computer Science

2015 - 2017

- I learnt the concept of programming with Java.
- Participated in some coding competitions.

- Built a web-based online admission system as my project.

Honors & Awards



Industrial Trainee of the Year - GTBank

Dec 2015

Skills

Laravel (PHP) • JavaScript • React.js • API Development • HTML5 • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • Heroku • Git • Trello • Figma (Software)